MENU

Privacy Policy
==============

Introduction
------------

Jeometri Insurance Managers (Guernsey) Limited is committed to protecting your personal information when you use our services and website. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide through the Jeometri website.

In order to provide you with the best experience, we are sometimes required to collect information about you.

Jeometri is committed to safeguarding your personal information. The material contained on the Site is for information only and does not constitute legal or other advice. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

**What information will Jeometri collect about me?**  
When you sign up to participate in or receive a service from Jeometri we may ask for personal information about you. This can consist of your name, email address and telephone number.

By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable Jeometri to provide you with the services you selected.

**What about cookies?**  
This website does not use cookies.

**How will Jeometri use the information they collect about me?**  
Jeometri uses your personal information in a number of ways including the following:

? to contact you about a submission you have made to the website, including any content you provide  
? to personalise the way we present content to you

**When will Jeometri contact me?**  
Jeometri may contact you:

In relation to any service you have signed up for where you have opted to receive further correspondence.

You may opt out of receiving marketing material and other information from us at any time. This can be done by unsubscribing from email communications at the bottom of each email, or by contacting us to have your details removed by emailing hello@jeometri.com

**Will Jeometri share my personal information with anyone else?**  
We will keep your information confidential except where disclosure is required or permitted by law (for example to government bodies and law enforcement agencies). Jeometri does not sell or otherwise transfer any personal data to commercial companies or other organisations.

**How long will Jeometri keep my personal information?**  
We will store your personal data on record and process it in accordance with this privacy policy until you either withdraw consent or because there is no legitimate reason for us to retain this data.

**Can I find out what personal information Jeometri hold about me?**  
You have the right to access any of the information that we hold on you. You have the right to have any inaccurate information corrected and you have the right to object to the use of your information for direct marketing. To exercise these rights, please contact us by writing to Jeometri at the address shown at the base of this page or email us using the link provided or hello@jeometri.com

**Changes to the Jeometri Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time so you may wish to check it each time you submit personal information our website.

**Links to other websites**  
The Jeometri website contains links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave the Jeometri site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website in question.

#### get in touch

ADDRESS  
Jeometri Insurance Managers (Guernsey) Limited  
3rd Floor, One Cornet Street  
St. Peter Port  
Guernsey  
GY1 1BZ  

PHONE  

EMAIL  

#### quicklinks

#### location

© 2022 Jeometri Insurance Managers (Guernsey) Limited Channel Islands  |  [Privacy Policy](https://www.jeometri.com/Jeometri_Insurance_Guernsey.html)  |  Site by: [Bazil](http://www.bazil.biz/Jeometri_Insurance_Guernsey.html)  
Some images courtesy of VisitGuernsey
